- Morning, roomie. - Hey!
-室友早！ -嘿！
You remembered to put clothes on this morning.
今天早上你記得穿上衣服了
Fifth day's a charm.
第五天終於記得了
It's so great to be back here. You're making it so easy on me and Emma.
能夠搬回來真好 你幫了我跟艾□一個大忙
It's great having you back. Stay as long as you want.
你能夠搬回來也真好 你要待多久就待多久
And when does she stop crying all night?
她什麼時候才不會哭一整晚呢？
Hey! You're not naked.
嘿！你沒有光著屁股
Rach, when will we expect to see you tonight?
瑞秋，你今晚什麼時候會回來？
Probably around 6. But she's in the bedroom, all ready to go.
大概六點吧，她在房間裡 已經準備好了
But she fell back to sleep, so..
她又睡著了，所以…
She's probably exhausted from all that adorable screaming she did last night.
可能是因昨晚美妙的哭聲而累壞了
- Bye. - Bye.
-再見 -再見
Hey, I hope Emma isn't making it too hard on you.
嘿，我希望艾□沒有帶來太多麻煩
No, hey, it's been great.
沒，嘿，一切都很好
I just want you to know that with Rachel staying here..
我只想讓你知道，雖然瑞秋住在這邊
all my feelings from before are totally over.
但是我之前對她的感覺早就已經沒了
And even if they weren't..
即使本來還有…
when you walk in on a woman using a breast pump..
當你看到一個女人用吸奶器…
- Yeah, that'll do it. - Wow!
-是啊，沒錯 -哇！
So how are you?
那你怎樣呢？
- I'm okay. - Really?
-不錯啊 -真的嗎？
Sure. I mean, do I wish me and Rachel living together would have worked out?
當然，我有沒有希望過 和瑞秋快樂地住在一起？
Of course. You know, I'm disappointed, but it's not like it's a divorce.
當然有，你知道的，我是有點失望 但是這又不像是離婚
- Well, actually it.. - It's not a divorce. It is not a divorce!
-嗯，事實上這… -這不是離婚，這不是離婚！
Anyway, I think Rachel and I need to get on with our lives.
反正我認為我跟瑞秋 應該要過自己的生活
Maybe start seeing other people.
或許開始跟其他人交往
Wow. Really?
哇，真的嗎？
Sure, why not? In fact, if you know anyone that'd be good for me..?
當然，為何不呢？ 事實上，你有認識適合我的人嗎？
- Sure. I know lots of girls. - Any names come to mind?
-當然，我認識很多女生 -腦海中有浮現任何名字嗎？
Names?
名字？
The One With The Blind Dates
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
- I was about to eat. Want something? - What you got?
-我才正要吃點東西，你要嗎？ -你有什麼呢？
Okay, let's see, we got strained peas, strained carrots..
好的，讓我看看，我們有豆子泥 胡蘿蔔泥…
strained plums. We haven't tried that yet!
梅子泥 我們還沒有試過這個！
Goody!
好棒！
Thanks.
謝謝
So how is it living with Rachel again?
跟瑞秋再住一起如何呢？
I mean, apart from the great food?
我是說，除了有很多好吃的之外？
I'm fine, I'm fine. It's just..
很好，很好，只是…
It's just weird what's happening with her and Ross.
她跟羅斯之間真的是很詭異
Yesterday he asked me to fix him up with somebody.
昨天他要我介紹女生給他
Rachel asked me if I knew anyone for her too.
瑞秋也問我有沒有男生可以介紹給她
- Why are they doing this? - I don't know.
-他們為什麼要這樣呢？ -不知道
They're so perfect for each other. It's crazy.
他們彼此再適合不過了，真是神經
You know what's crazy? These jars.
你知道什麼才神經？這些罐子.
What is there, like, two bites in here?
才兩口就沒了？
I just wish they'd realize they should be together.
我只希望他們可以發現 彼此是適合在一起的
When they moved in together, I figured that's where things were headed.
當他們一起住時, 我以為事情就解決了
They should be a family. They should marry and have more children.
他們應該是一家人 結婚生更多的小孩
Yes. And they should name one of their kids Joey.
是啊，而且該把其中一個取名叫喬伊
I may not have kids. Someone's gotta carry on the family name.
我或許不會有小孩 總是要有人幫我傳承香火吧
You know what? Maybe once they start dating and see what's out there..
你知道嗎？或許他們一旦開始 跟別人約會，知道別人是怎樣的…
they'll realize how good they are for each other.
他們就會發現彼此是多麼適合
Yeah, because it is slim pickings.
是啊，因為他倆真是絕配啊
I had this date last night. Yuck!
我昨晚約會的女生遭透了，討厭！
But we should probably keep it down, she's still in the bedroom.
但是應該要說小聲一點 她還在房間裡面
So, what are we gonna do? Are we just gonna set them up with people?
那我們該怎麼做呢？ 我們要幫他們介紹人嗎？
I know, that just pushes them further and further apart.
我知道，這樣只會使他們漸行漸遠
I know what we can do. We could set Ross and Rachel up on horrible dates..
我知道要怎麼做了 我們可以幫羅斯跟瑞秋介紹可怕的人
so they'll realize how good they are together.
讓他們發覺彼此是很好的
- That's a great plan. - Yeah.
-真是好計劃 -是啊
You know what the best part of it is? I get to do my plan laugh.
你知道最棒的是什麼嗎？ 我可以來個計劃成功之笑
Okay, shh! Not so loud. We don't want to wake up..
好了，噓！不要那麼大聲 不要吵醒…
Hi. You guys aren't doing anything tonight, are you?
嗨，你們今晚沒有計劃，對嗎？
See, now, why would you assume that? Just because we're married?
為什麼你為那樣以為呢？ 就因為我們已經結婚了嗎？
I mean, I will have you know that we are very hip, happening people.
我是說，我要讓你知道 我們是非常時髦好玩的人
Now if you'll excuse me, I have to get back to reading the obituaries.
現在不好意思，我要回去讀報上訃聞了
I was just asking because I need someone to watch Emma tonight.
我會問是因為 今晚我需要有人幫我帶艾□
Sure we'll do it. What are you up to?
當然我們可以，你要做什麼呢？
- Well, Phoebe set me up on a date. - Oh, my God.
-嗯，菲比幫我安排一個約會 -喔，天哪
- Why? What's the big deal? - I figured because you and Ross are..
-為什麼？有什麼不對嗎？ -我以為你跟羅斯是…
What? Slept together a year and a half ago? Yeah, I'm all set.
是怎樣？一年半前上過床嗎？ 是啊，那我就全搞定了
I think it's great you're going on a date. It sounds healthy.
我認為你能夠去約會是件好事 聽起來很健康
I mean, you have needs. Embrace your womanhood.
我是說你有你的需要 面對你的女性特質吧
You want a job? Turn off Oprah and send out a resume.
你要找工作嗎？關掉新聞挖挖哇 然後去寄履歷表
- I'll bring her by around 7, okay? - That's perfect.
-我七點左右帶她過來好嗎？ -太棒了
You guys are gonna have so much fun. She's at such a cute age.
你們會很開心的 她現在正是可愛的時候
A couple things. Now that she eats solid food, she poops around the clock.
有幾件事，現在她會吃固體食物了 所以會按時排便
And watch out for your hair because she likes to grab it.
還有小心你的頭髮，因為她喜歡抓
She's also in this phase where if you leave the room, she screams, but..
這時期的她還會在 你離開房間的時候大叫，但是…
Thanks, you guys. Have fun.
謝謝你們，祝你們玩的開心
Suddenly I wish I was reading my own name.
突然間，我希望自己的名字在上面
Joey, hey. I'm so excited.
喬伊，嘿，我好興奮
- I set Rachel up with the worst guy. - All right. Who is he?
-我幫瑞秋約了一個最糟糕的男生 -好的，是誰呢？
It's a guy I used to massage. By "massage"..
是我曾經按摩過的一個男的 而「按摩」時…
I mean hold down so he wouldn't turn over and flash me.
我得按住他 讓他不能轉身露鳥
- Wait till you hear who I got for Ross. - Oh, yeah.
-等你聽聽我介紹誰給羅斯再說吧 -喔，好啊
Okay. She's this really boring woman. She's a teacher.
她真是個很無趣的女人 她是個老師
- A teacher? - She's into history and foreign movies.
-老師？ -她喜歡歷史跟外國影片
And she loves puzzles.
而且她喜歡益智遊戲
Come on, who loves puzzles?
拜託，誰會喜歡益智遊戲呢？
Well, Ross does.
嗯，羅斯喜歡啊
You're ruining the plan!
你毀了計劃了！
Joey, you fixed him up with his perfect woman.
喬伊，你把他的天生另一半介紹給他了
- Oh, my God, you're right! - Yeah.
-我的天，你說的沒錯！ -是啊
She even reads for pleasure!
她甚至還喜歡讀書！
- How do you know a woman like that? - I'm not allowed to know smart women?
-你怎麼會認識那種女人呢？ -我不能認識聰明的女人嗎？
- Joey? - We met at the library. I went in to pee.
-喬伊？ -在圖書館，我進去上廁所時認識的
- So now what do we do? - Well, okay.
-那我們現在該怎麼辦呢？ -嗯，好吧
I'll call her and tell her the date's canceled and find him somebody else.
我打電話跟她說取消 然後再找別人
What if we don't find him somebody else? We'll just tell her the date's off..
要是我們找不到別人呢？ 我們只要跟她說約會取消了…
but we don't tell Ross. He'll go to the restaurant and get stood up.
但是不要跟羅斯說 他會去餐廳等，然後被放鴿子
I hear that's bad.
真是太壞心了
So this is great. Rachel's gonna have a terrible date..
太棒了，瑞秋會有個很糟糕的約會
Ross gets stood up, and then they'll realize how good they have it together.
羅斯被放鴿子，然後他們會發現 對方才是最好的
Yes, the plan.
是的，好計劃
It's not Santa's plan.
這不是聖誕老公公的計劃
No, it's..
不，這是…
- Yeah, you know, it's not that fun. - No, I think we killed it.
-你知道嗎？不太好玩了 -是不好玩，我們弄僵了
Emma? Emma, look at me!
艾□？艾□？瞧瞧我！
Well, I think I'll go downstairs for a while.
嗯，我想我要下樓一下子
No, no, no! It's okay! It's okay! I didn't go!
不！沒關係！沒關係！我沒有去！
Don't cry, it's just a bit!
別哭，我是開玩笑的
I'm your Uncle Chandler. Funny is all I have!
我是你的錢德姑丈，我只會搞笑啊！
Okay, just so you know, I'm gonna be ovulating from tomorrow until the 6th.
好了，讓你知道一下 我從明天開始到六號都在排卵
So don't touch yourself for the next 48 hours.
所以接下來的四十八小時 你可別自慰
I don't do that.
我不自慰的
I'll try to stop.
我會試著克制自己
- Did you say until the 6th? - Yeah.
-你是說到六號嗎？ -是啊
Today is the 6th.
今天就是六號
No, it's not.
不，不是
Yes, it's also 2003.
是的，而且是2003年
Oh, my God. Today's the 6th?
我的天，今天是六號？
I may be done ovulating!
我可能已經排完了！
I may have also served some very questionable meat at the restaurant.
我在餐廳做的肉類 或許都很有問題
- Go take the test, see if we're okay. - Okay.
-去做測試，看是不是還好 -好的
Tough crib.
定力不錯啊
Hey, where are all my ovulation sticks? There's only one here.
嘿，我其他的排卵測試劑呢？ 只剩下一個了
I might have checked to see if I was ovulating a couple times.
我可能拿了幾個測試看 我是不是有排卵
I'm not working! There's not much to do around here!
我沒有工作，沒事做很痛苦的
（德莫尼可餐廳）
Sorry. You want a roll with that?
抱歉，還需要麵包嗎？
Excuse me.
不好意思
Is there a woman waiting at the bar?
有沒有一個女人在吧檯那邊等人呢？
Someone average height, dark hair? Or perhaps doing a puzzle?
不高不矮，黑髮？ 可能在玩猜謎遊戲？
There's a drunk Chinese guy.
是有個喝醉的中國人
Well, if I'm still here in an hour, buy him a drink on me.
嗯，如果我一小時之後還在這裡 幫我請他喝一杯
Can I get you another glass of wine?
您要不要再點一杯酒呢？
I don't know if I should. I don't want to be drunk when I..
我不知道應不應該 不想喝到醉醺醺的，然後…
go home alone tonight.
今晚獨自回家
- Got stood up, huh? - It's no big deal. It's just a blind date.
-被放鴿子了，是嗎？ -沒有什麼，只不過是跟陌生人約會
Are you worried your date came, saw you and left?
你擔心那個女的一來 看到你就走了嗎？
No!
不！
We're okay. I'm still ovulating.
還好，我還在排卵
Oh, good, because as of 4:00 this afternoon, I am not.
很好，因為今天下午四點的時候 我沒有在排卵
So let's do this.
那我們來嘿咻吧
- I don't think I can. - Oh, come on.
-我想我沒辦法 -喔，別這樣
I know you're not 18 anymore, but give it a minute.
我知道你不是十八歲了 但是給它一點時間啊
- Because of Emma. - Oh, my God, Emma.
-因為艾□的原因 -天啊，艾□
Oh, sweetie, I forgot you were here.
親愛的，我忘記你在這裡了
You're right, we can't do this. We can't leave her alone.
你是對的，我們不能這樣做 我們不能單獨留她在這裡
Sorry.
對不起
Unless..
除非…
maybe we do it here.
或許我們可以在這裡做
I mean, how much can she even be aware of at this age?
我是說，她這個年紀懂什麼呢？
She's aware when we leave a room. She may notice if we start..
我們離開房間她都知道 或許她也會注意到我們…
canoodling in it.
在親熱
- Canoodling? - Well, I can't say hump or screw..
-親熱？ -嗯，我總不能在一個娃娃面前說…
in front of the B-A-B-Y.
做愛或是上床吧
I don't know, I guess having sex in front of a baby..
我不知道，我想在嬰兒面前做愛…
- isn't so.. - Horrifying? Scarring?
-不是很… -可怕？嚇人？
Something people go to jail for?
沒有人因此而坐牢？
- I guess you're right. - You guess?
-我想你說的對 -你想？
At that bed-and-breakfast, we didn't have sex..
住在民宿的時候，我們沒做愛…
because you thought a deer was staring through the window.
因為你認為有隻鹿站在窗外看
Well, what kind of a sick bastard wants to do it in front of a deer?
什麼樣變態的人 想要在一隻鹿面前做愛呢？
Wow, everything looks so good.
哇，每樣東西看起來都很好吃
I think I'm gonna have the chicken.
我想我要點雞肉
I just have to say this.
我必須要這麼說
- You're really beautiful. - Wow, that's very sweet. Thank you.
-你真的很漂亮 -哇，這真是貼心，謝謝你
I'm kind of funny-looking.
我長得有點好笑
- What? - Look, I mean, come on..
-什麼？ -聽著，我是說少來了
you're way out of my league. Everybody in here knows it.
你不是我可以高攀的起的 這裡每個人都看得出來
I bet that guy over there is probably saying:
我敢說那邊那個男的 可能在想…
"Why's she out with him? He must be rich."
「為什麼她會跟他出來呢？ 他一定是很有錢」
Well, I'm not.
可是，我並不有錢
Okay.
好吧
Well, I guess, then the joke's on him.
嗯，那我想，算是他的問題好了
What do you think you want to order? I'm real excited about that chicken.
你想要點什麼呢？ 我真的很期待他們的雞肉
I'm not funny, either.
我也不風趣
So if you were thinking, "Well, he's not that good-looking..
所以如果你是在想 嗯，他倒是不太好看…
but maybe we'll have some laughs, " that ain't gonna happen.
但是也許他很幽默 那你就錯了
Well, come on, Steve, let's not rule out nervous laughter.
別這樣，史提夫 我們不要讓彼此尷尬
So, now, I think that we should order..
所以現在，我想我們應該點餐了
and then eat, and then leave.
然後用餐，然後再離開
I have a lot of medical problems.
我一身是病
Hey, now, wait a minute, Phoebe told me..
嘿，等等，菲比告訴我…
that you owned your own restaurant. That's impressive.
你是自己開餐廳的，真是了不起
I lost it to drugs.
我因為吸毒把餐廳頂讓了
I silk-screen T-shirts now.
我現在做絹印T恤
Really? What's that like?
真的？做得怎樣呢？
It's really fulfilling doing something you hate for no money.
做你痛恨的工作、又賺不到錢 真是非常充實啊！
That's right. I have no money, I'm not funny..
沒錯，我沒有錢，又不風趣
I live in a studio apartment with two other guys.
住在一間沒有隔間的公寓 跟兩個男的一起生活
And I'm pretty sure I'm infertile.
而且我很確定，我有不孕症
Now, come on. Come on, Steve.
別這樣，別這樣，史提夫
There must be something that you like about yourself.
你一定有什麼自己喜歡的地方
I do like my hair.
我是挺喜歡我的頭髮的
Really?
真的嗎？
（中央咖啡廳）
- Hello? - Phoebe, it's me!
-哈囉？ -菲比，是我
I'm going to hunt you down and kill you.
我一定要追殺你、把你給剁了
Hey, Rach!
嘿，瑞秋
This is the worst date ever! How could you set me up with this creep?
這真是史上最爛的約會！ 你怎麼可以介紹這個怪人給我呢？
You know, you are talking about one of my dear, dear friends.
你是在批評我最要好的朋友耶
I don't care. This guy is a nightmare.
我不在乎，這個人是個惡夢
All right, so he gets a little crazy when he's stoned.
好了，他只不過在 吸毒的時候才有點失常
- He's not stoned. - Did he go out for a cigarette?
-他沒吸毒 -他有出去抽煙嗎？
- Yeah. Four times. - My dear, sweet Rach.
-有啊，四次 -我親愛的甜姐兒瑞秋
Well, our plan is working. Rachel's having a miserable time..
我們的計劃奏效了 瑞秋如坐針氈
and Ross is stood up somewhere at a restaurant all alone.
而羅斯正一個人在某家餐廳呆坐 被放鴿子了
Pretty soon they'll be back together.
他們很快就會復合了
By the time anyone's figured out what we've done, we'll be in sunny Mexico.
等到大家發現我們做的好事時 我們早就在陽光普照的墨西哥了
Oh, wait, that's the end of a different plan.
喔，等等，那是另一個計劃的結局
She's asleep. Chandler?
她睡著了，錢德？
- What are you doing? - Emma was doing it.
-你在做什麼呢？ -艾□也都這樣做啊
She's asleep.
她睡著了
- She's asleep. That means we can.. - Yes. But we have to be fast.
-她睡了，表示我們可以… -是的，但是我們必須要動作快
Oh, okay, I'll try.
喔，好的，我盡量
- And you can't make any noise. - Okay, I'll try.
-而你不能發出任何聲音 -好啦，我盡量
Hello?
哈囉？
Emma?
艾□？
Hey! Hi!
嘿！嗨！
How are you? How are you?
你好嗎？你好嗎？
Where are your babysitters, huh?
你的保姆們呢？
Why is the bedroom door closed?
為什麼房間的門是關著的呢？
You can't have S-E-X when you're taking care of a B-A-B-I-E.
在照顧小孩的時候是不能嘿咻的
I've got bad news. The Chinese guy left.
我有個壞消息，那個中國人走了
If it was meant to be, it's meant to be.
如果不是命中注定，就不是命中注定
Look, you got stood up. Who cares?
聽著，就算是被放鴿子又如何呢？
We're gonna show you a good time. Sit and relax.
我們會好好招待你，你好好坐著享受
In fact, let me bring you a crab-cake appetizer on the house.
事實上，讓我免費招待您 蟹肉餅當開胃菜
Wow, free crab cakes? Well, that's nice.
哇，免費的蟹肉餅嗎？真是周到
Although I was hoping to have sex tonight.
雖然我本來希望今晚可以嘿咻一下的
Just the crab cakes.
只要蟹肉餅就行了
What are you doing? Are you trying to get him to stay? You can't do that.
你在做什麼？要把他留下來嗎？ 你不可以那樣
- Just get out of here, okay? - I'm sorry, what's going on?
-不要多管閒事好嗎？ -很抱歉，這是怎麼回事？
Okay, the waiters have a little pool going.
服務生們都在打賭
We have a bet on how long it'll take before you give up and go home.
賭你會等多久才會放棄 回家去
What?!
什麼！
You're making money off my misery?
你們拿我的悲慘境遇來贏錢？
Well, if you stay till 9:20, I am.
嗯，如果你待到九點半，我就贏了
This is unbelievable. I have never been so insulted in my life.
太離譜了，我從未被如此羞辱過
Now, if you'll wrap up my free crab cakes, I'll be on my way.
現在如果你幫我把蟹肉餅打包 我就馬上離開
Well, that was weird. You were loud and I was fast.
真是奇怪，你倒是很大聲 我倒是挺快的
I think we may have really done it this time.
我想我們這一次可能會成功
I wish I didn't have to wait to take a pregnancy test.
我希望我不用等到作驗孕測試
You may want to get some more of those too.
你可能需要再多買一些
Where's Emma?
艾□呢？
Oh, my God, where's Emma? Where's Emma?
我的天，艾□呢？艾□呢？
Don't ask me. I was in there canoodling you.
別問我，我跟你在裡面親熱
Okay. Okay. I'm sure that Rachel came home early and picked up Emma.
好吧，我想應該是瑞秋提早回來 把艾□帶回去了
You go look across the hall, and I'll call her cell.
你去對面看看，我來打電話給她
You better hope we're pregnant..
你最好祈禱我有懷孕
because one way or another, we're giving a baby back to Rachel!
因為無論如何 我們得要有個嬰兒可以還給瑞秋！
I can't believe I'm crying in front of you.
我不敢相信我在你面前哭泣
You must think I'm so pathetic.
你一定覺得我很可悲
No, no, no, I admire a man who can cry.
不、不、不，我欣賞會哭的男人
- Really? - Don't touch my coat.
-真的？ -別碰我的外套
Sorry, that's my phone.
對不起，我有電話
- Hello? - Hey, Rach, how's it going?
-哈囉？ -嘿，瑞秋，進行的怎樣呢？
Oh, my God, this is the worst date ever.
我的天，這是我有過最爛的約會了
Oh, come on.
喔，少來了
Look, you know what, I'm sorry, but did you really think that this was going well?
聽著，我很抱歉，但是你真的認為 一切進行的很順利嗎？
- What's up? - Hey, did you stop by here?
-怎麼了？ -嘿，你有來過嗎？
- No. - Oh, my God! Then..
-沒有 -喔，我的天，那…
Thank God! Emma, there you are!
感謝上帝！艾□原來你在這裡！
What? What do you mean, "there you are"? Where was she?
什麼？「原來你在這裡？」 是什麼意思，她在哪裡？
We were playing peekaboo. She loves it when I'm dramatic.
我們在玩躲貓貓 她愛死我的激情演出了
- Why the hell did you take her? - Because you two were having sex!
-你為什麼要帶走她呢？ -因為你們兩個在做愛！
- No, we weren't. - Don't you lie to me.
-不，我們沒有 -別對我說謊
I can tell by Chandler's hair. You are so lazy. Can't you get on top for once?
我從錢德的頭髮就可以看出來 你真懶，你就不能有一次在上面嗎？
All right. All right, we were.
好啦，好啦，我們是在做愛
We're trying to make a baby. Monica's ovulating.
我們是要努力懷孕，摩妮卡正在排卵
Which is more than I can say for myself as of 2:00 today.
我今天下午測自己的時候都沒有呢
Guys!
你們…你們…
Seriously, those sticks are expensive!
說真的，它們很貴的！
It's unacceptable that you'd have sex with Emma in the next room.
有艾□在這裡 你們就不能在裡面做愛
- I'll have to tell Rachel about this. - Please don't. She will kill us.
-我必須要告訴瑞秋這件事 -拜託不要，她會殺了我們的
Hey, I gotta. Unless..
嘿，我一定要，除非…
Unless what?
除非怎樣？
Unless you name your first-born child Joey.
除非你們把第一個小孩取名叫喬伊
- What? Why? - Hey, I may never have kids..
-什麼？為什麼？ -嘿，我可能永遠都不會有小孩
and somebody's gotta carry on my family name.
總是要有人幫我延續香火 用我家的姓吧
Your family name is Tribbiani.
你姓崔比亞尼
You almost had me.
你差點就騙過我了
Look..
聽著…
I think I know the answer to this question, but..
我想我知道這個問題的答案，但是…
would you like to make love to me?
你想要跟我做愛嗎？
Really, really not.
真的，真的不想
It's just as well.
只不過是問問
It doesn't work anyway.
反正也沒有希望
All right, well, that's good to know. Good night, Steve.
好的，那就這樣，晚安，史提夫
- Hey, what's wrong? - I just had a rough night.
-嘿，怎麼了？ -我剛度過糟糕的一晚
Crab cake?
要蟹肉餅嗎？
Well, what happened?
發生什麼事了？
This is kind of weird to talk to you about this, but..
跟你聊這件事真的是有點奇怪 但是…
Monica told me you had a blind date.
摩妮卡跟我說你去約會了
- Yeah. - I did too.
-是啊 -我也是
But is it technically a date if the other person doesn't show up?
但是如果對方沒有出現 那到底算不算是約會呢？
Oh, no. Do you think she walked in, saw you and left?
喔，你覺得是她看到你 然後就走了嗎？
Why does everyone keep saying that?
為什麼大家要一直這樣說呢？
If it makes you feel any better, I wish my date hadn't shown up.
我可以讓你好過點 我真希望我的對象沒有出現
- That bad? - Well, he makes T-shirts for a living..
-那麼糟嗎？ -他是做T恤的
and he thought it would be appropriate to give me..
而且他認為送這樣的禮物給我是…
this.
很適當的
（聯邦調查局 女性身體檢查官）
"Female Body Inspector"?
「女性身體檢查官」？
What size is that?
這是什麼尺寸的？
Now wait a minute. So they're gonna name their first child Joey?
等等，所以他們要把 第一個孩子取名喬伊？
How do I get them to name the next one after me?
那我要怎樣才能讓他們 把第二個孩子以我的名字取名呢？
It's easy. You just walk in on them having sex.
很簡單，你只要在 他們做愛時走進去就行了
Oh, so they owe me, like, three Phoebes.
喔，所以他們已經欠我三個菲比了
Oh, my God! Look, it's Ross and Rachel!
我的天！瞧，那是羅斯跟瑞秋
The plan is working!
計劃奏效了
Don't do the plan laugh.
別再做那個計劃成功之笑了
The first dates we've had in months, and they were both such disasters.
我們幾個月以來的第一次約會 而結果卻這麼慘
You know, it is weird..
你知道，真是奇怪…
that Phoebe would set me up on a date that was awful..
菲比幫我安排一個很爛的約會
on the same night Joey set you up on a date that didn't even show.
而在同一晚，喬伊幫你安排了一個 根本沒有人出現的約會
Wait a minute.
等一下
You don't think it was intentional?
你不會認為這是故意的吧
I mean, that's just stupid.
我是說，這實在太愚蠢了
We're geniuses.
我們真是天才
- Look at them! They're really bonding. - They're falling in love all over again.
-瞧瞧他們！合得不得了 -再度墜入愛河了
Oh, they see us. Oh, they look mad.
喔，他們看到我們了，看起來很生氣
They figured it out. They're coming. Run!
他們知道了，他們過來了，快跑！
- Where? - Mexico!
-跑去哪？ -墨西哥！
Can you believe they're still not here?
誰敢相信她們居然還沒有出現？
I know. A double blind date and we both get stood up.
是啊，雙對約會 我們竟然一起被放鴿子
What are the chances?
怎麼可能呢？
I know, I'm so bummed.
我知道，我好難過
Could we have our free crab cakes now?
現在可以上免費的蟹肉餅了嗎？
- What? - We've been stood up.
-什麼？ -我們被放鴿子了
And we want our free crab cakes.
我們想要上免費的蟹肉餅了
- You were stood up here last night. - I know. It hurts.
-你昨晚才在這裡被放鴿子 -我知道，真是傷心
Being stood up two nights in a row has left a crab cake sized hole in my heart.
一連兩晚被放鴿子，已在我心中留下 像蟹肉餅一樣大的傷口了
Guys, give it a rest. Nobody's betting on you tonight.
你們倆，不用裝了 今晚沒有人在拿你們打賭
Although we do have a pool going to see how long it takes that guy to cry.
不過我們倒是有在賭 看那個男的多久才會哭
I have such fat hands!
我的手好肥
I hate my dick!
我恨我的小雞雞